Contact

halle.horn@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/halle-holloway-5b697053 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing
Home Care
Patient Education

Halle Holloway

BSN,RN- Travel Nurse

Greater Nashville Area, TN

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Customer Service, Wound Care, Medical-Surgical, Medication Administration, and Life Support. Strong healthcare services professional with a BSN focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Cumberland University.

Experience

Several Companies
Travel RN
June 2011 - Present (9 years 1 month)

CareAll Home Care Registered Nurse

Parallon Business Solutions RN,BSN November 2012 - Present (7 years 8 months)

Midde Tennessee Medical Center Floor RN June 2010 - December 2012 (2 years 7 months)

Education

Cumberland University
BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2007 - 2010)

Westchester high General · (1999 - 2003)